pathfinderwiki.com 2018-12-31

# PathfinderWiki:Privacy policy - PathfinderWiki

 | 

**This page is anofficial policy on the PathfinderWiki.**  
It has wide acceptance among editors and is considered a standard that all users should follow. 

In accordance with policy, this page has been protected. You can suggest changes by following the revision procedure or discussing it on the talk page").   
  
---|---  
  
### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To credit you for your contributions to the website
     All edits made to the website are tracked so that the work you put into the project can be credited to you.
To verify account creation requests
     In order to curtail spam, we request information about you so that we can verify you intend to be a productive member of the website community.

### Do we use cookies?

Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.) 

We use cookies to save your preferences for future visits. 

If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, you will need to manually log in to the website each time you want to make an edit or employ your personal settings. 

### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. We may release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. In some cases, personally identifiable information may be shared with trusted third parties who wish to contact particularly helpful or influential wiki contributors (generally these trusted third parties are staff members of Paizo Inc.). 

### California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into the wiki and going to the 'Preferences' page (by click the menu on your user name, at the top of the screen). 

### Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act). We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to this privacy policy. 

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. Revisions to this policy may be monitored by viewing the page's history. 

This policy was last modified on June 26, 2017. (Updated Preferences link location, adjusted punctuation; no policy changes.)
